Sir, the insurance company is in a lot of buzz.
In May, there has been a significant increase in the premium of General Insurance Company,
which is approximately 15% and the
premium has crossed Rs 908 crore.
If we talk about the premium of New India Insurance, there
is an increase of 0.7% in it, there is 9.3% in Harias and at the same time,
we have seen an increase of approximately 21.6% in ICI Labd. What do you
think, how can we see the overall insurance sector in the
coming time?
Any picker stock, choice of a new firm,
is such a sector which is still on. If we
talk about India, people are still hesitant
in taking insurance, but we will see now. A lot of
bad news has come in the last few days, so people are
concerned about it and they are getting serious,
that is why this big rise has come, so
my view is that I advise against such stocks, this is not a one-time investment
of manufacturing
companies where you will get multi-billion returns
here.
I feel it is very difficult to get a return of 15-20, so my advice is
that you can invest for diversification but
its share in the portfolio should not be
kept too high and my well-proven pick is
ICICI Lod Funds from ICI Group, ILO
General Insurance, it has given a good spike today and the
all-time high is near AKM, so it is not advisable to invest
it
today, it has
given a good spike today, it is
almost at 5
today, right, about the insurance sector
and at the same time,
you can keep an eye on ICICI Lombard,
Vishal.